Blanchard, Duncan; Papers ua902.065
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1900-2003; 3; 7.8 cubic ft.
  - Beard, Ken, 1973-1974; 1984-1987; 1989-1990; 1992 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Benninghoff, William, 1976; 1980; 1983; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Bergeron, Tor, 1962; 1971-1974; 1977-1980; 1989 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Bezdek, Hugo, 1972-1973; 1975; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Bikerman, Jacob, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Bjornsson, Sveinbjorn, 1964-1969; 1988-1989; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Bonmarin, P., 1980; 1982 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Bowen, E.G., 1951; 1955-1956; 1961 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Bowyer, Peter A., 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Branson, Charles, 1970; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Brown, Hugh, 1959 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Buck, Robert, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Burger, Scott [RESTRICTED], 1978-1982 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Burger, Scott, 1983-1992 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Burndy Library (Bern, Dibner), 1970; 1974; 1997 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Burstyn, Harold, 1979; 1981 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - C, 1949; 1953-1954; 1960-1962; 1964-1965; 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - C, 1970-1981; 1983-1985; 1987-1990; 1994-1999; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Cacciola, J., 1966 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Chang, Sam [RESTRICTED], 1970; 1972-1974; 1976-1977; 1980-1983; 1985-1987 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Chang, Sam [RESTRICTED], 1991-1993; 1997; 2000; 2002; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Caporizzo, Steve, 1992; 1994; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Cardon, Bartley L., 1977; 1980-1984; 1986; 1990-1991; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Carlucci, A.F., 1974; 1976-1977 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Chare, Keith, 1970; 1979; 1981-1982 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Cheng, Roger, 1978; 1986-1987; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Chesselet, Roger, 1970-1971; 1977; 1980 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Charley, Harold, 1978 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Cini, Renato, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Cipriano, Ramon, 1976; 1978-1979; 1984; 1986-1997; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Cole, Robert, 1980-1982 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Candell, W.J., 1975 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Conrad, William, 1969; 1978-1980 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Cooke, R.C., 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Craighead, Frank, 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Craft, Tony, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Crum, Lawrence, 1981; 1983 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 63)
  - D, 1952; 1966-1967; 1971-1972; 1974-1976; 1979 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 64)
  - D, 1981-1984; 1986; 1988-1989; 1993 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 65)
  - D, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Daniels, R.W., 1966 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Davis, Herbert L., 1970-1973 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 68)
  - Day, John, 1962-1973; 1975; 1980-1981; 1983; 1990-1991 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Day, John, 1993; 1995-1996; 1999-2000; 2002; 1789/2003 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - De Juhasz, Kalman J., 1964-1968; 1970 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - deLeeuw, Gerrit, 1985-1987; 1996 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Demerjian, K [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Densmore, Dana, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Denrenzo, Dave, 1979; 1981; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - de Santillana, Giorgio, 1965 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Dessens, Jean, 1979 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Detwiler, Andy, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Dewan, Edmond, 1929; 1978; 1980; 1989-1991; 1994-1995 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Dewan, Edmond, 1997; 1999-2000; 2002-2003; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Dimmick, Robert L., 1976-1977 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Dingle, A. Nelson, 1956; 1966 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Dolezalek, Hans, 1962; 1969; 1971; 1973 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Dow, Corning, 1951-1953 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Droessler, Earl G., 1976; 1979; 1986; 1993; 1996 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Duce, Bob, 1963-1964; 1967-1972; 1974; 1978-1982 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Duce, Bob, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Dudley, H.C., 1961; 1963 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - DuPont, 1959 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - E, 1949; 1952; 1954-1955; 1960-1961; 1963 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - E, 1970-1974; 1976; 1980; 1982-1983; 1985 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - E, 1987; 1993; 1997 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Edmonds, Robert, 1978-1979; 1983 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Ellis, Robert, 1964 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Erickson, David, 1985-1988 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Errors in Books, 1900; 1962; 1972-1974; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Euein-Kebe, John Boris, 1976; 1979-1986; 1988; 1991; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - F, 1955-1956; 1959; 1961; 1963-1964; 1970-1972 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - F, 1974; 1976-1978; 1980-1981; 1983; 1985-1989 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - F, 1994-1996; 1998; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Falconer, Ray, 1949; 1953; 1980; 1984; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Falkinham, Joseph, 1981; 1983-1984; 1988; 1994; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Farnham, Jack, 1984; 1988 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Fischer, William, 1965 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Flake, Wilbur, 1973-1974; 1977; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Flanagan, Vincent, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Freudenthal, Peter, 1967; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Fullerton, C.M., 1967; 1969-1970; 1973; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - G, 1952-1953; 1955; 1959; 1961-1966 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - G, 1970-1980; 1982-1987; 1997; 2000; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Gaines, Arthur, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Gailson, Peter, 1987-1988 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Garbalewski, Czeslaw, 1973-1974; 1988/1990 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Garrett, William D., 1965-1969; 1972-1975; 1977-1978; 1980-1982; 1984 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Garrett, William D., 1987; 1999; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Gathman, S., 1969 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - George, Carl, 1982; 1988; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Gershey, Bob (R.M.), 1981-1986; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Giles, C.H., 1971 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Giles, Lester A., 1960 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Gillies, William, 1967-1969 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Godard, L., 1960-1961 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Goetz,Alex, 1968; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Gokhale, Narayan R., 1963; 1978-1979 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Gold, Mike, 1973; 1975; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Goncharenko, A., 1989-1990 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Goroch, Andy, 1980; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Goupil, Dennis, 1973-1976; 1978; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Grave, Eric, 1975; 1984-1991; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Greene, Evelyn, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Greene, Mott, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Gruft, Howard, 1971-1979; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 64)
  - Gunn, Ross, 1951 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Gucinski, Herman, 1976-1980; 1983-1984 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Ha-, 1953; 1955; 1959; 1963; 1965 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Ha-, 1969; 1971-1974; 1976-1977; 1979-1981; 1983 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 68)
  - Ha-, 1986-1987; 1989; 1991; 1998 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Hankin, Steve, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Hannan, Jerry, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 71)
  - Hardy, Kenneth, 1966; 1973 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Harper, J.F., 1972-1973 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 73)
  - Harris, Karen, 1974-1976 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 74)
  - He-, 1952; 1954; 1959; 1961; 1963 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 75)
  - He-, 1969-1970; 1974; 1978; 1997 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 76)
  - Healy, Jim, 1965; 1969 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 77)
  - HejKal, Thomas, 1976; 1980; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 78)
  - Henderson, Thomas, 1963-1975 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 79)
  - Hi-, 1952-1953; 1962; 1964; 1971-1973; 1975-1976 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 80)
  - Hi-, 1979-1980; 1986-1987 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 81)
  - Hickman, K.C., 1963; 1966 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 82)
  - Hill, Bob, 1986; 1994-1995 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 83)
  - Hill, Maynard, 1972 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 84)
  - Hitchcock, W.S., 1977; 1980 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 85)
  - Ho-, 1951; 1955; 1957; 1962; 1964-1967 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 86)
  - Ho-, 1969; 1971-1975; 1977; 1987; 1989 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 87)
  - Ho-, 1993; 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 88)
  - Hobbs, Peter, 1964; 1966; 1968-1969; 1972; 1985 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 89)
  - Hoffman, Eva, 1972; 1974/1979; 1984/1985; 1789/2003 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 90)
  - Hogan, Austin, 1970-1971; 1973; 1992 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 91)
  - Holton, Gerald, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 92)
  - Horne, R.A., 1965-1968; 1972; 1976-1977 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 93)
  - Houghton, Henry G., 1955; 1966; 1970; 1972-1973; 1989 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 94)
  - Hs- to Hu-, 1961; 1963; 1973; Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 95)
  - Hu-, 1977; 1981; 1984-1985; 1987 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 96)
  - Hudson, N.W., 1959-1960; 1964 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 97)
  - Hughes, Jim and ONR, 1952; 1954; 1956-1957; 1961-1971; 1975 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 98)
  - Hughes, Jim and ONR, 1978-1980; 1982-1984; 1986; 1997; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - I, 1952; 1962; 1964; 1973; 1982 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Indian Correspondence, 1953; 1956; 1959; 1961; 1968-1969 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Indian Correspondence, 1977-1978; 1982-1983; 1988; 1990; 1992 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Indian Correspondence, 1995; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Ingersoll, Andrew, 1959-1961; 1982; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Iribarne, J.V., 1965; 1967; 1970; 1973; 1979 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Iribarne, J.V., Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Ironkwe, O.Paul, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - J, 1951-1952; 1963-1964; 1968; 1970; 1972 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - J, 1974; 1976; 1978-1979; 1981-1986; 1996-1997 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - J, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Jaenicke, Ruprecht, 1978; 1982 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Japanese/Chinese Correspondence, 1955-1956; 1959-1960; 1962-1963; 1965-1966; 1968-1969 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Japanese/Chinese Correspondence, 1971-1978; 1980-1983; 1986-1990 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Japanese/Chinese Correspondence, 1992; 1998-1999; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Jelks, M.L., 1974 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Jennings, S. Gerard, 1975-1976; 1983 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Johnson, Bruce, 1977-1981; 1983; 1986-1990; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Johnson, Dave, 1952-1954 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Jones, Peter, 1974 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Junge, Christian, 1963-1964; 1972 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - K-, 1951; 1954-1955; 1957-1959; 1961-1967; 1969 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - K-, 1970-1978; 1981; 1984; 1986; 1989-1990 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - K-, 1996; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Kalvoda, Peter, 1991-1993 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Kane, Julius, 1962; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Kaysing, C.W., 1962; 1965-1966 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Keith, Charles, 1952 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Kerman, Bryan, 1982-1983; 1985; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Kershner, William, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Kjelleberg, Staffan, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Knight, Charlie, 1988; 1990; 1992-1993; 1995; 1999 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Knight,Charlie, 2003; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Koeing, L. Randall, 1963-1965 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Koenigsberger, Otto H., 1954; 1956-1957 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Kohler, Hilding, 1957; 1972-1973 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Kramer, Morris, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Kraus, Eric, 1969; 1981 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Krener, John, 1956-1957 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Kritz, Mark, 1980-1981; 1985; 1995 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - L-, 1952-1954; 1957; 1959; 1964-1965; 1967-1969 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - L-, 1971-1978; 1980-1986; 1990-1991; 1993-1994 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - L-, 1998-2000; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Longford, Ken, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Latham, John, 1963-1967; 1969; 1974; 1978; 1983 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Latham, John, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Leipper, Dale, 1961; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Lemlich, Robert, 1971-1973; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Le Mone, Peggy, 1982; 1984 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Lenton, Tim, 1998 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Leong, K.H., 1984; 1986 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Lepple, Fred, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Letters from Students, 1967; 1981-1983; 1989; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Letters of Reference -A-J [RESTICTED], 1967; 1970-1974; 1978-1988; 1990-1993 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Letters of Reference -A-J [RESTICTED], 1996; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Letters of Reference -L-Y [RESTICTED], 1965; 1967-1980; 1983-1986; 1998; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Lewis, John, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - List, Roland, 1961; 1964; 1970-1971; 1976-1977 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Lodge, James, 1961; 1966; 1977-1978; 1990 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Loeb, Leonard, 1956-1957; 1959-1967; 1971; 1978; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Lopez, Michael, 1996-1999 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Lovett, Richard F., 1978-1980 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Ma-, 1951-1952; 1954-1956; 1960; 1963; 1966-1967 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 64)
  - Ma-, 1969; 1972-1974; 1976-1977; 1980-1983; 1985 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Ma-, 1987; 1990; 1998; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 66)
  - MacCready, DePaul, 1963; 1965; 1971 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Maciejewski, Jacek, 1981-1982 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 68)
  - MacIntyre, Farren, 1963; 1968; 1972-1976; 1978-1986; 1988-1989 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 69)
  - MacIntyre, Farren, 1991-1992; 2002; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Macker, P.K., 1967 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 71)
  - Macpherson, Alistair, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Manten, A.A., 1963 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 73)
  - Margulis, Lynn, 1977 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 74)
  - Marks, Colin, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 75)
  - Marks, Roman, 1989-1991; 1995; 2001; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 76)
  - Markson, Ralph, 1976; 1981; 1984; 1987; Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 77)
  - Manuscript Reviews (1956-1982), 1956-1957; 1960-1961; 1963-1971 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 78)
  - Manuscript Reviews (1956-1982), 1972-1975 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Reviews (1956-1982), 1976-19780 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Reviews (1956-1982), 1981-1982 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Reviews (1983-Present), 1983-1985 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Reviews (1983-Present), 1986-1988 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Reviews (1983-Present), 1989-1993; 1996-1997 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Martson, Philip, 1981-1983 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Martell, Edward, 1979; 1989-1993 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Martin, Dean, 1982; 1986 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Mason, Stanley, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Matthews, J. Brain, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - May K.R., 1969; 1974-1975 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Mc-, 1952; 1958; 1961; 1964; 1973 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Mc-, 1975-1977; 1984; 1988; 1990 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Mc-, 1992; 1996 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - McCutchen, C.W., 1970-1972 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - McDonald, Ray, 1981-1982 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - McLaren, Gene, 1985 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Me-, 1958-1959; 1974; 1976-1977; 1980; 1982 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Me-, 1984; 1989-1991 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Medrow, Robert, 1963-1964; 1971; 1978 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Medwin, Herman, 1972; 1978; 1989; 1991 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Mee, Tom, 1963; 1965; 1969-1970; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Melland, Robert, 1969; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Menthe, Robert, 1963 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Mesler, Russell, 1976; 1979; 1982; 1985; 1988 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Mi-, 1963; 1968; 1976; 1978; 1980-1982 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Mi-, 1994; 1998-1999; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Michnowski, Stanislaw, 1971-1973; 1977; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Miller, Charles, 1971; 1973; 1975-1976 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Miller, James, 1972; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Mo-, 1949; 1965-1966; 1968; 1971-1972; 1974 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Mo-, 1984-1986; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Mohnen, Volker [RESTRICTED], 1974; 1976-1977; 1979-1985; 1987; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Monahan, Ed, 1965-1972; 1974; 1976-1979 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Monahan, Ed, 1980-1991; 1997; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Moore, A.D., 1913; 1931-1932; 1945-1946; 1950-1951; 1954-1955 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Moore, A.D., 1959; 1962-1964; 1966-1972 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Moore, A.D., 1973-1982 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Moore, A.D., 1983-1989; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Moore, Charles, 1950; 1956-1957; 1960-1966; 1970/1971; 1973 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Moore, Charles, 1975-1977; 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Mordy, W.A., 1952-1956; 1965; 1973; 1978-1979; 1983 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Mordy, W.A., 1992; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Morelli, Jacques, 1974-1976; 1980; 1982-1983 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Morley, R.J., 1964; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - MRI(Meteorology Research Inc.), 1965-1967; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Mu-, 1966; 1973; 1981; 1984 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Muhleisen, R., 1958-1959; 1962; 1964; 1968-1969; 1971 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - My-, 1964; 1973; 1985 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - N-, 1953; 1957; 1961-1963; 1968; 1971-1975 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - N-, 1977; 1979; 1981-1982; 1985-1986; 1998 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Namias, Jerome, 1983-1984 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Neuberger, Hans, 1951; 1953; 1955-1956 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1962; 1972; 1985 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Nursall, Allan, 1988 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - O-, 1961; 1963; 1968; 1970; 1974-1976 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - O-, 1981; 1986; 1989 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Oliosi, Fabio, 1981-1982; Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Oruille, Richard, 1970-1971; 1979; 1986-1988; 1990-1991 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 60)
  - P-, 1954-1959; 1961-1965; 1967; 1969-1978; 1980 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 61)
  - P-, 1983; 1988-1990; 1997 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Parker, Bruce, 1969-1979 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Parker, Bruce, 1980-1981; 1983; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Pattenden, N.J., 1981-1982; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Patterson, Albert, 1962 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Patterson, Mark, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Pereira, Martin, 1973-1977; 1979; 1981-1983; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Phillips, Braden, 1994 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Photo Requests, 1958; 1962-1964; 1968; 1970; 1972-1977 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Photo Requests, 1979; 1981-1985; 1988-1989; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Pierce, Allan, 1972 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Pierce, Richard, 1986-1988; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Plumb, R.C., 1971 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Podzimek, Joe, 1959; 1971; 1975; 1977-1981; 1983 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Podzimek, Joe, 1985; 1988 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Prospero, Joe, 1968; 1972; 1978; 1980 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Prospero, Joe, 1982; 1993; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Q-, 1974-1975; 1988-1989 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - R-, 1951; 1953-1954; 1958-1963; 1966; 1968 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - R-, 1970-1976; 1978; 1980-1981; 1983-1984; 1986 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - R-, 1991-1993; 1997; 1999; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Rakeshaw, Norris, 1961 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Randall, Davis, 1962-1963 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Rango, Art, 2000 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Renn, Charles, 1964; 1981-1990 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Renn, Charles, 1991-1999; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 24)